esaabparts.com 2016-12-10

# eSaabParts.com

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, postal address and other information ("Personal Information").

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.

We use "cookies" to customize the site content to the choices you explicitly make. For the most part, cookies are used so you can maintain your session when revisiting the site. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.

Whichever cookie preference you choose, under no circumstances do any third-party parties have access to any data/information you create or input on our site.

The security of your Personal Information is extremely important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use industry leading means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

That being said, we use HTTPS encrytion on 100% of the site content so your interaction with us is entirely encrypted.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
